{
    "id": "2d91f6378ac64312bb753caebe2a8f03",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We will cancel the trip ……………………….. it rains.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We will not cancel the trip …………………………. it rains.",
            "description": "Even if refers to future. Even if means no matter what.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "even if",
                "even though"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was acquitted …………………………… he was guilty.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "because",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was freed ………………………….. he was innocent.",
            "description": "Because expresses the reason for something.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "because",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no doubt ………………………… the earth moves around the sun.",
            "description": "That is used to introduce a noun clause.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "as",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not get the job …………………………. you deserve it.",
            "description": "Unless means if not.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost his balance …………………………… fell off the ladder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is richer ………………………. I am.",
            "description": "Richer is a comparative expression use than after it.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "compared to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You will never succeed …………………………. you try.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if not",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I were you, I wouldn’t tolerate this.",
            "description": "If is used to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Make hay …………………………. the sun shines.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "while",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I trust him ………………………… he is honest.",
            "description": "For can mean because.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}